//An array of questions and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
        answer: "Sadio Mane",
        options: [
            "Gareth Bale",
            "Sergio Ag√ºero",
            "Sadio Mane",
            "Mohammed Salah"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "With 260 goals, who is the Premier League's all-time top scorer?",
        answer: "Alan Shearer",
        options: [
            "David Beckham",
            "Alan Shearer",
            "Christiano Ronaldo",
            "Fredrik Ljungberg"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How many clubs competed in the inaugural Premier League season?",
        answer: "22",
        options: [
            "22",
            "20",
            "18",
            "24"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "When was the inaugural Premier League season?",
        answer: "1992-93",
        options: [
            "1991-92",
            "1989-90",
            "1992-93",
            "1995-96"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which country won the first ever World Cup in 1930?",
        answer: "Uruguay",
        options: [
            "France",
            "Uruguay",
            "Brazil",
            "England"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which country has won the most World Cups?",
        answer: "Brazil",
        options: [
            "Brazil",
            "Mexico",
            "Spain",
            "England"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which club has won the most Champions League titles?",
        answer: "Real Madrid",
        options: [
            "Liverpool",
            "Milan",
            "Barcelona",
            "Real Madrid"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Who is the Champions League's top goalscorer of all time?",
        answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        options: [
            "Rivaldo",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Leo Messi",
            "Alan Shearer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which outfield player appeared in the Champions League final in three different decades?",
        answer: "Ryan Giggs",
        options: [
            "Ryan Giggs",
            "David Beckham",
            "Ronaldo",
            "David Trezeguet"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who are England's third most successful team in Champions League with two titles?",
        answer: "Nottingham Forest",
        options: [
            "West Ham",
            "Arsenal",
            "Nottingham Forest",
            "Tottenham"
        ]
    },
];